const questions = [
  {
    question: "Can I take a demo session?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can book a free session. You will be connected to a personal mentor from IIT/AIIMS for a one-time 30-minute session.",
  },
  {
    question: "How does the mentoring process work?",
    answer:
      "Our mentoring platform connects mentors and mentees through an online matching system in groups of six. Mentors and mentees can then communicate and schedule sessions through our platform.",
  },
  {
    question: "How many students will be assigned to one mentor?",
    answer:
      "Six. After you register for the mentorship program, you will be matched in groups of six with a mentor.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I and my friends have the same mentor?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can. You need to separately register for your individual programs, and our team will sort you into one group with the same mentor.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I find a mentor?",
    answer:
      "To find a mentor on our platform, you will need to create an account and complete a short profile outlining your goals and areas of interest.",
  },
  {
    question: "Can I change my mentor?",
    answer:
      "Yes, you can change your mentor. First, our team will investigate your problems with the current mentor, and when they feel that you are not in resonance with your mentor, then your mentor will be changed.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Are there any fees associated with using your mentoring platform?",
    answer:
      "Yes, there are fees associated with using our mentoring platform. We have three kinds of subscription plans. You can check them out in the mentoring plans section.",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I cancel my account on your mentoring platform?",
    answer:
      'You will need to log in to your account and navigate to the "Account Settings" section. From there, you can follow the prompts to cancel your account.',
  },
  {
    question: "How will I get my refund?",
    answer:
      "You must email us at info@careervyas.com, and your fee will be refunded to your bank account within a week/",
  },
  {
    question: "Is my number shared with the mentor?",
    answer:
      "No, your privacy is our topmost priority. Your information is safe with us and would not be shared with any third party.",
  },
];

export default questions;
